{
    "subject": "\u00c9ric_Rochant",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Patriots__film_",
    "human_readable": "\u00c9ric Rochant directed the film The Patriots.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9004184603691101,
            "question": "Name a film directed by \u00c9ric Rochant."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8400154709815979,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by \u00c9ric Rochant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8231343030929565,
            "question": "Who directed the film The Patriots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7465624213218689,
            "question": "Is \u00c9ric Rochant a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6886273622512817,
            "question": "Has \u00c9ric Rochant directed any other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2711119055747986,
            "question": "Who are some actors who might have been in The Patriots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25703948736190796,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of The Patriots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24685537815093994,
            "question": "What year was The Patriots released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18824701011180878,
            "question": "What genre is The Patriots likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17616121470928192,
            "question": "Where could I watch The Patriots?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=\u00c9ric Rochant directed the film The Patriots.",
            "html": "yago_12213_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is The Patriots likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_12213_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was The Patriots released?",
            "html": "yago_12213_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of The Patriots?",
            "html": "yago_12213_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12213_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents confirm that Eric Rochant directed the film \"The Patriots,\" which is further supported by details about its release, plot, and cast."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}